Diego Goslar

Full Stack Developer

Phone: 8644176215 Email: lgoslsar@gmail.com

SUMMARY

3+ years of experience in full stack development. Loves a challenge and the ability to conceptualize new projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS	QUALIFYING SKILLS
 Java C# Salesforce Godot Python INET HTML/CSS JavaScript API Development Dashboard Management Jira Salesforc 	Avidity to acquire knowledge and absorb new

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lieus Chinese Bistro October 2023 - Present

Server

- Provides outstanding customer service
- · Helps with food preparation and restaurant upkeep
- Provides assistance in physically strenuous tasks

Vision-e April 2023 - September 2023

Salesforce Developer

- Completed a company wide automated emailing service within a week
- Steadily yet excellently learned flow and approval logic
- Developed Subject Matter Proficient status in Salesforce development

T-Mobile July 2022 - August 2022

Software Developer Intern

- Learned SQL and completed an API within 6 weeks
- Communicated with 3 other interns on ongoing assignments for Microsoft SQL Server and basic API construction in Python
- Made C.R.U.D databases within Python

T-Mobile June 2021 - August 2021

Software Developer Intern

- · Completed a simple yet versatile inventory management system in Java
- Experienced an 8-week baptism by fire in Java
- Presented a final C.R.U.D application to a board for interns
- Joined team members in participating in company held events

EDUCATION & LANGUAGES

Certificate - Greenville Technical College

Major: Computer Science

High School Diploma - J.L Mann

English: Native

Japanese: Intermediate Vietnamese: Beginner